leigh warner

CONTACT

128 Donomore Avenue

D24 V1Y5

E-mail: leighwarner3@gmail.com **Website:** https://leighwarner99.github.io/,

 $\underline{https:/\!/www.linkedin.com/in/leigh-warner-}$

34baa0166/

Phone: 0858486800

PROFILE

Recent graduate from Technological University Dublin where I obtained my degree in Computer Science with Data Analytics. Acquired my knowledge and experience from working on projects while attending college and my internship. Vast knowledge of programming languages, OS troubleshooting, cloud technologies, and Database languages. I am extremely excited to join a workplace and bring my skills and knowledge to the company and further my expertise in the field.

EDUCATION

Computer Science with Data

2017 - 2021

Analytics

Technological University Dublin

Final GPA - 3.0 (2:1)

Modules Studied: Applied Artificial Intelligence and Deep Learning (**C+**), Enterprise Performance Architecture (**B+**), IT Governance and Quality (**b-**), Project (**B**), Interactive Media Design (**B+**), Information Management (**C+**), Social Media Analysis (**A**), Data Analysis and Programming (**C+**), Applied Machine Learning (**B-**).

Software Development with Games

2016 - 2017

Design

Greenhills College

Modules Studied: Web Authoring, Networking, Games Design, Software Architecture. Math's, Fundamentals of Object Oriented Programming, Mobile Technologies, Work Experience, Communications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electrical Supply Board

January 2020 — August 2020

Enterprise Services

- Provide constant feedback/support to manager about day to day tasks.
- Maintaining a clean working environment.
- Automating day to day tasks with the use of PowerShell scripting.
- Point of contact for the creation of user account's through the MDMS Database.
- Obtaining information through SQL scripts about new incoming meters, analyzing the meters making sure that the information was correct and the meters were AMR ready
- Attend weekly meetings and take notes.

The Galway Hooker

November 2018 — December 2019

Bar man

- Confidently managed EPOS systems over a 12-month period, handling various transactions including the processing of refunds, returns as well as cash and card payments.
- Skillfully served beer, wine, spirits, non-alcoholic drinks and custom cocktails throughout my time as a bartender.
- Maintained a clean and organized bar area while attending to countless customer needs
- Maintained a safe environment by discontinuing service to intoxicated guests and coordinating with staff to defuse conflict.

leigh warner

- Maintained extensive knowledge of wines, cocktail recipes, beers, and promotions to provide quality recommendations to guests.
- Meticulous professional with comprehensive experience placing stock orders and managing inventory.
- Address customer service complaints while maintaining a friendly and clam demeanor.

PROJECTS

Final year project overview:

Emotion detection through image classification

Data selection and preparation of images to expand the dataset for further development of the network. Training the data using Python's built-in libraries such as **Tensor Flow**, **Pandas**, **NumPy**, and **SkLearn**. Development and fine tuning of **Convolutional Neural Networks** to gain the best models for predictions on unseen data. Use of pre-existing CNN models like **VGG-16**, **RESNET-50**, and **Inception-V3**. Predictions made on unseen images to allow models to accurately make predictions on the seven basic human emotions. Compared my own models to pre-existing models for comparison to made conclusions on overall best models.

e-Commerce website overview:

Vintage Vinyl Factory

This project consisted of a three-man team in which an e-commerce website was designed using UML, Play Framework, Scala, JavaScript, eBeans DB,

Bootstrap, and **jQuery**. During the creation of the e-commerce site, bootstrap was used throughout for design and added functionality throughout the site. There was a **CRUD** system in placewhich allowed for different level of users to access the site, users such as administrator, manager, and a regular user. We implemented **Stripe** for our cart functionality, which allowed for fake transactions to occur to simulate real-time transactions taking place. The project was conducted within an **Agile** environment which included reporting to our supervisor each week on further developments within the project.

IT SKILLS

- Coding languages Java, C++, Python, C#, JavaScript, PowerShell
- Designing websites using HTML, CSS, Scala, Bootstrap, NoSQL, SQL
- Efficient user of Windows and Linux Operation Systems
- Understanding of Machine Learning & AI model based development
- Knowledge of AWS technologies
- Capable user of cloud computing concepts such as **Databases**, **Networking**, **Routing**, **Switches**, **IP/DNS**, **OSI Model**.

INTERESTS

- Reverse game engineering
- Extreme sports
- Guitarist in a band
- Volunteer local clean ups within the area

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

leigh warner 2